Guide to the NURTUREart records CBHM.0025
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 1: Artists' Registry
  - Sub-series 1.1: A-Z Files
    - Tinajero-Baker, Patricia, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Timberlake, Emily, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Tio, Miguel, circa 2002 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Tisa, Charles, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Tobin, Nancy, circa 2006 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Toinon, Veronique, circa 1999 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Tondro, Cassie, circa 2006 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Toole, Christa, circa 2006 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Tordia, Radish, circa 2004 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Toro, Arnulfo, circa 2005 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Torres, Marisa, circa 2008 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Tosk, Barbara Ann, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Tower, Cindy, circa 2007 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Trager, Adrienne, circa 2005 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Trepte, Cody, circa 2006 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Trigg, Sarah, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Triplett, Ginna, circa 2003 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Tsensarskava, Marina, circa 2003 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Tsers, Andrey, circa 2005 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Tucker, Margaret, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Tung, Eugenie, circa 2007 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Turbek, Joanmarie, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Turnage, JP, circa 2008 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Turner, Annie, 2010 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Twomey, Chris, circa 2006 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Ueda, Reona, circa 2006 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Ungar, Joanne, circa 2006 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Josetta Urso, 2009 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Vadera, Jaret, circa 2003 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Valdez, Julio, circa 2001 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Valdez, Kim Carr, circa 2008 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Valeri, Sarah, circa 2009 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Valla, Teressa Hopkins, circa 2004 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Van Anden, Jason, circa 2004 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Vanderberg, James, 2009 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - VanDyke, Jonathan, 2009 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Van Houten, Lori, circa 2008 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Van Leeuwen, Gerda, circa 2003 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Dekker-Vargas, Claudia, circa 2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Vautier, Mireille, circa 2007 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Verwer, Yona, circa 2005 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Vialu, Carlo, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Viegas, Mariana, circa 2004 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Vieira, Cibele, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Vierstra, Kai, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Villanueva, Fred, circa 2005 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Villasmil, Alejandra, circa 2004 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Vinette, Julia, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Vinton, Thomas, circa 2001 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Vogel, Conrad, circa 2006 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Vollmer, April, circa 2007 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Vought, Lynette, circa 1998 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Wainer, JE (Hota), circa 2000 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Waldstein, Justin, circa 2006 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Waligore, Athena, circa 2004 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Walker, Sarah, circa 2005 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Wallis, Danielle Giudici, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Walpole, Cynthia, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Walsh, Patrick, circa 2002 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Walsh, Peter, circa 2001 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Walter, John, circa 2006 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Wang, Elizabeth, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Warck Meister, Lucia, circa 2003 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Ward, Clay, circa 2001 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Ward, Sean, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Wasserman, Deborah, circa 2005 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Waters, Claudia, circa 2008 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Wathen, Sarah, circa 2007 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Watkins, Ryan, circa 2005 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Watkinson, James F., 2009 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Watson, Claire, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Watson, Katie, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Weber, Debra, circa 2000 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Weber, Matthew, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Weber, Michael, circa 2005 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Webster, Charles, circa 2000 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Webster, Derrick, circa 1999 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Weinblatt, Lisa, circa 2002 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Weis, Betsy, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Weisberg, Debra, circa 2008 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Weiss, Lawrence, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Weitzman, Eileen, circa 2005 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Welsh, Michael, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Wendel, Sara, circa 2005 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Westheimer, Bill, circa 2003 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Whitaker, Corinne, circa 2006 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - White, Joanna, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - White, Kathyanne, circa 2002 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - White, Lili, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Whitman, Phil, circa 2007 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Whitmore, Russell, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Wight, Sarah, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Wilcox, Randal, circa 2001 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Kelly, circa 2007 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Williams-Myers, Maluwa, circa 2002 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Willis, Corey J., circa 2003 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Kristina, circa 2004 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Winberg, Ellie, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Winika, Cynthia, circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Winters, Veronica, circa 2007 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Wintje, Kim, circa 2004 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Wikniewski, Gene, circa 2008 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Wofsey, Tammy, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Wojcik, Mark, circa 2007 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Wolert, Beatrice, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Wooh, Suhee, circa 2009 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Woolridge, Joeseph, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Woronoff, Beth Gabrielle, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Wren, Rachel, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Wren, Rachel, 2009 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Wroblewski, Jennifer, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Wu, Hsuan Hsuan, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Wu, Moonching, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Wyndham, Tamara, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Xavier, Ricardo, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Yale, Melinda, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Yamada, Joyce, circa 2007 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Yanes, Jacob, circa 2004 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Yankus, Marc, circa 2002 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Yaniro, Michael, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Yassin, Aaron, circa 2002 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Yeapanis, Stacia, circa 2006 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Yarrington, Debra G., 2008 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Yeh, CJ, circa 2001 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Yeoman, Claire, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Yeung, King Yan Fina, circa 2003 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Yhuel, Cedric, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Yoo, Haeri, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Yoo, Stella, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Yoon, Bohyun, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Yossen, Patricia, circa 2005 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Yuan, Seldon Shi Chi, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Yun, Pauline, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Zacharow, M. Christopher, circa 2001 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Zaccagni, Hope, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Zadlo, Frank, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Zanis, Liz, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Zanisnik, Bryan, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Zdatny, Ian, circa 2004 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Zhang, Jenny, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Zhao, Quanzhou, circa 2005 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Ziccardi, Jill, circa 2004 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Zimmerman, J.G., 2008 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Zimmermann, Virginia, circa 2002 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Zippel, Egon, circa 2001 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Zito, Antony, circa 2000 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Zizioli, Chiara, circa 2005 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Zlotsky, Deborah, circa 2006 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Zorreguieta, Dolores, circa 2002 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Zoubkous, Boris, circa 2001 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Zweibel, Jan, circa 2007 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Sub-series 1.2: Incomplete submissions
    - Belfer, Karen Starrett, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Bowen, Dianne, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Brammeier, Heather, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Cammermeyer, Kristin, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Chang, Victoria H., 2009 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Cybil, Vladimir, circa 1999 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Deceus, Francks, circa 1996 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Epstein, Robert Otto, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Engels, circa 2000 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Ezer, Merav, circa 2006 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Frett, Yael E. [?], circa 2012 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Gedeon, Christine, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Juste, Andre, circa 1997 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Krebs, Beth, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Kukla, Michael, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Landes, Barbara, circa 2005 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Lawrence, Scott, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Leboeuf, Ray, circa 1999 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Loutrel, Lara, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Luciani, Giuseppe, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - McCorkle, Summer, circa 2006 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Mishin, Hannah, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Mitrano, Ray Ray, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Mukhtar, Helene, circa 2006 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - NÜTRO, circa 1998 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Oates, Leah, circa 2010 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Lalileo, Maia Cruz, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Penn, Jeremy, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Peralta, Ramon, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Peterson, Tiana, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Picha, Brendan, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Pidel, Lynne A., circa 2008 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Potts, Rebecca, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Puckett, Courtney, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Reich, Rikki, circa 2003 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Ro-Sa, circa 2009 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Rogers, Dylan, circa 2005 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Ruey, Rosa, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - Saint Jean, Fritz, circa 2005 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Sears, Dennis L., 2009 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Julie, circa 2001 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Stern, Emily Beth, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Stuttman, Paula, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Surno, Molly, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Swartelé, Amy, circa 2009 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Tamiesie, Stephen, circa 2009 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Thompson, Adam, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Unrein, Suzanne, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Vieira, Cibele, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Jennifer, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Oscar, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Yu, Jing, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Yumiko, circa 2004 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Zlotsky, Deborah, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Series 2: Exhibits
  Series 2: Exhibits is arranged in four sub-series:
  Sub-series 2.1: Artist materials is arranged chronologically by exhibit.
  Sub-series 2.2: Administrative and planning materials is arranged chronologically by exhibit.
  Sub-series 2.3: Emerging Curators' Program exhibit proposals is arranged chronologically.
  Sub-series 2.4: Promotional materials and clippings is grouped by topic and arranged chronologically.
  Sub-series 2.1: Artist materials were originally housed in binders organized by exhibit name and arranged chronologically. Materials in this sub-series include examples of artwork submitted for exhibits, inventories, promotional materials, and contracts. There is a significant overlap with materials in the following sub-series.
  Items in sub-series 2.2: Administrative and planning materials were not held in binders and have been arranged by the archivist. Items include press releases, promotional materials, agreements and contracts, photographs, slides, sales documents, correspondence, contact information, and artist submissions (slides, disks, prints). In addition to exhibits, this sub-series includes planning and administrative documents concerning panels and talks. Exhibits produced for Project Curate are also included. Sub-series 2.3: Emerging Curators' Program exhibit proposals includes proposals that were not accepted. Paperwork for accepted proposals is held in sub-series 2.2. Additional media is held in box 72.
  - Sub-series 2.1: Artist materials
    - ARCHI + TEXTURE, 2003 (Box 69, Item 1-4)
    - White Matter(s), 2004 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Fantastical Memories, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Messing Around, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Dear Bubble Tea, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - cracker: re-thinking the american south, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - PAPER, PAPEL, PAPIER..., 2005 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - It was here a minute ago, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Another place, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Structuring Perception, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - MAD COW, Absurdity and Anxiety in Contemporary Culture, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Once Upon a Time 1, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Well Read, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - ITER-ITER-ATION, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - please OPEN the door, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - The Occidental Artist, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Quote, Unquote, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Subjects of Power and Devotion, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Bodies of/at Work, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - At Arms Length, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - MY LITTLE/MEMBRANE, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Politics and Other Diversions, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Present Perfect Continuous, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - ENANTIOMORPHIC CHAMBER, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - SERIAL MEDITATIONS, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Demo Eco M.O., 2008 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Seen/Unseen, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Patterns of Growth, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Interface: Nature, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Bushwick Biennial, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Plan B, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Collage: Collage, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Eternal Return, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - DUCK AND DECORATED SHED, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - THE NEW INTIMISTS, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season I, 2010-2011 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season I Media, 2010-2011 (Box 69, Item 1-14)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season II, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Blood, Sweat and Tears: The Work of Art and Tragedy, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Soft Power, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Scott Kiernan: Once around the block (twice), 2011 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - The Constructed Landscape, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Juxtacombo, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - The escape from the banal everyday life to the world of the ideal, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Scott Lawrence: Monochrome, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Videorover: Season 4, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - ...Is This Free?, 2012 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Can I Take This?, 2012 (Box 90, Folder 3, Folder Flat File)
    - The Order of Things, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Siobhan McBride: Never While You're Sleeping..., 2013 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Marysia Gacekm, Natalie Häusler, Katharina Marszewski: On the Golden Wire for Thirty-Four, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Cashing Out, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Videorover: Season 5, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Antoine Lefebvre: There are no accents on my qwerty keyboard, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - On Hold, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - The Indifference of Wisdom, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Liz Sweibel: fragments of our own, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - The Psychic Triangle, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Alina Tenser: Hip Openers, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Videorover: Season 6, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Videorover: Season 7, 2013-2014 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - One Trace After, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Jenny Santos: The Thing That's There But Isn't, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - To begin, at the beginning, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - #ArtistsBeLike, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - MaryKate Maher: Braced Position, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Multiplicity (Part 1), 2014 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Yasi Ghanbari: Yo! I'm Your C.E.O., 2014 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Brain Scratch, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Just Mad Art Fair, 2015 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Gabriela Salazar: My Lands are Islands, 2015 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Rational Formal, 2015 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Ciarán Ó Dochartaigh: Upward Inflection, 2015 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - What it Was, 2015 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - NURTUREart at NEWD, 2015 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Videorover: Season 8, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Videorover: Season 9 Workshop Series, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - SEXTANT, 2015 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Davide Zucco: Deep Time, 2015 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Jesse Harrod: Low Ropes Course, 2015 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Dustin London: Scared of Dying, 2015 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Lior Modan: Wringing Lilies from the Pine Nut, 2015 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Codes for Conduct, 2016 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Steffani Jemison: Prime, 2016 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Dead Lands: Karkaot Mawat, 2016 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Our Crazy Life, 2016 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Ellie Krakow: Arm Armature, 2016 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Exhibit media, various artists, circa 2012-2016 (Box 86, Item 1-25)
    - Retrospective photograph albums, circa 1998-2007 (Box 87, Binder 1-2)
    - Slides, 2001-2002 (Box 87, Binder 3)
    - Axe, 2013 (Box 89, Item 1)
      General
      Axe was presumably acquired as part of an exhibition. It has been illegibly signed by the artist and dated 2013.
  - Sub-series 2.2: Administrative and planning materials
    - Press Releases: Exhibits, Panels, and Talks, 1998-2004 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - NURTUREart at the Consulate, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - NURTUREart in NoHo, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Reaction, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - NURTUREart off Broadway, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - NURTUREart in Harlem, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - NURTUREart Reaches the Heights, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - NURTUREart at X, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Messages, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Workshop: The Secrets of Shooting Super Slides, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Fresh, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - "Me" In the Art World: Information-Enhancement-Working Knowledge, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Deye Mon-Beyond the Mountain, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - A Virtual Tour of the Contemporary Art Scene in France, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - The Post-It Show/Inside a Bigger Box, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - ID-ENTITY, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Too Fresh, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - PULP, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - ARCHI + TEXTURE, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - The Mouth Breathers, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - PROJECTIONS: 3 screenings, 7 video artists, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
    - HORIZONTAL WAVES: New Takes on Landscapes, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 3-4)
    - Fantastical Memories, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - MESSING AROUND, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Diving into the Details, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Artists' Books, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - White Matter(s), 2004 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - LMCC Winter Exhibit: In the Face of Others, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Six Windows, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Structuring Perception, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Dear Bubble Tea, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - ID Troubles- US Visit, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - cracker: re-thinking the american south, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - PAPER, PAPEL, PAPIER..., 2005 (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    - It was here a minute ago, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Well Read, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Once Upon a Time 1, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 2-4)
    - MAD COW: Absurdity and Anxiety in Contemporary Culture, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Another Place, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Please Open the Door, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - ITER-ITER-ATION, 2007 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - The Occidental Artist, 2007 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - QUOTE, UNQUOTE, 2007 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Subjects of Power and Devotion, 2007 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Bodies of/at Work, 2007 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - My Little Membrane, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Present Perfect Continuous, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - SCOPE Hamptons, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Enantiomorphic Chamber, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - SERIAL MEDITATION, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Politics and Other Diversions, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - DEMO ECO M.O., 2008 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - At Arms Length, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Social (Virus), 2009 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Patterns of Growth, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Seen/Unseen, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Bushwick Biennial, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
    - Collage: Collage, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - PLAN B, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Interface: Nature, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - IDLE TIME/BUSY MIND, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Eternal Return, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - The New Intimists, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Duck and Decorated Shed, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Who's Afraid of Ornament?, 2010 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Human Scale, 2010 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season I, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - We Are, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Clean Slate Club, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Scott Kiernan: Once around the block (twice), 2011 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Constructed Landscapes, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Open Jury Call, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - P-TOWN, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Re-Telling, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Portrait of a Soul, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Live and Let Die, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season II, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season II Media, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Blood, Sweat and Tears: The Work of Art and Tragedy, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - ...Is This Free?, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Svetlana Mircheva: Possible Exhibitions, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Systemic Risk, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Arianna Carossa: Argo, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Anne Percoco: The Life Instinct, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season 3, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - The escape from the banal everyday life to the world of the ideal, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Juxtacombo, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Daniel Bejar, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Open Call Jury, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season 4, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season 5 Program #2, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season 7, 2013 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Hip Openers, 2013 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Open Call Jury, 2013 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - On the Golden Wire for Thirty-Four, 2013 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - On Hold, 2013 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Parts to the Whole, 2013 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Bushwick Open Studios Weekend-There are no accents on my qwerty keyboard, 2013 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Cashing Out, 2013 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Golden Age: Perspectives on Abstract Painting Talks, 2013 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - The Psychic Triangle, 2013 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - The Order of Things, 2013 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Brain Scratch, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Yo! I'm Your C.E.O., 2014 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Multiplicity, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Multiplicity (Part 1), 2014 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Open Call Jury, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - To Begin, At the Beginning, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - One Trace After Another, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Jenny Santos: The Thing That's There But Isn't, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - #ArtistsBeLike, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Open Call Jury, 2015 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Upward Inflection, 2015 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Eyeroll, 2015 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Scared of Dying, 2015 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Jesse Harrod, 2015 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Just MAD, 2015 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Wringing Lilies from the Pine Nut, 2015 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - VIDEOROVER: Season 9/Workshop Series, 2015 (Box 67, Folder 6)